Guide to the Mark Weinbaum Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1896-1968; Series III; 0.25; (1 box) + 1 art storage item
  - Tschystiakov, Grigorii Tschystiakova, Frieda: medical documents (German), 1952 Jul (Box 14, Folder 598)
  - Scriabina, Kira: oil portrait of Weinbaum, undated (Box 17 (Art), Folder 598a)
  - Weinbaum, Mark
    - Article "Kherbert Khuver i pechat'," in Illustrirovannaia Rossiia with photograph of Hoover with Weinbaum, 1928 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 599)
    - Honorary membership of the Union of the survivors of the Lienz tragedy, 1956 Feb 12 (Box 14, Folder 600)
    - Newspaper clipping: photograph of Lyndon Johnson with Weinbaum (Box 14, Folder 601)
    - Newspaper clippings
      See: Oversize, Box 15, folder 606
    - "Notes about Mark Weinbaum" by Mrs. Weinbaum: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 602)
    - Notes from co-editor?, [1963?] (Box 14, Folder 603)
    - Slovo L. D. Rzhevskogo": [necrology?], 1973
      See: Oversize, Box 15, folder 608
    - Unidentified photograph, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 604)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1896-1968, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 605)
- Oversize, 1.75; (1 box)
  Box 15 holds chronologically arranged oversize papers.
  - Weinbaum, Mark: newspaper clippings, 1948-57, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 606)
  - Review of Na raznye temy by IUrii Terapiano in Russkaia mysl', 1957 Feb 23 (Box 15, Folder 607)
  - "Slovo L. D. Rzhevskogo": [necrology?], 1973 (Box 15, Folder 608)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.25; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 2 (Box 16, Folder 609)
  - Box 1, folder 20 (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Box 1, folder 22 (Box 16, Folder 611)
  - Box 1, folder 42 (Box 16, Folder 612)
  - Box 1, folders 44-45 (Box 16, Folder 613)
  - Box 1, folders 47-48 (Box 16, Folder 614)
  - Box 3, folder 117 (Box 16, Folder 615)
  - Box 4, folders 150, 157 (Box 16, Folder 616)
  - Box 5, folders 207, 227-28 (Box 16, Folder 617)
  - Box 5, folders 232, 234 (Box 16, Folder 618)
  - Box 7, folder 306 (Box 16, Folder 619)
  - Box 7, folder 316 (Box 16, Folder 620)
  - Box 7, folder 325 (Box 16, Folder 621)
  - Box 8, folders 354-56 (Box 16, Folder 622)
  - Box 9, folder 387 (Box 16, Folder 623)
  - Box 9, folders 424, 431 (Box 16, Folder 624)
  - Box 9, folders 434, 439 (Box 16, Folder 625)
  - Box 9, folders 442-44 (Box 16, Folder 626)
  - Box 9, folder 459 (Box 16, Folder 627)
  - Box 10, folder 474 (Box 16, Folder 628)
  - Box 11, folder 515 (Box 16, Folder 629)
  - Sibirskii, Konstantin: Chernaia ten' nad moim solnechnym zavtra: printed, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 630)
  - Box 14, folder 589 (Box 16, Folder 631)